Happy New Year!
Happy New Year
Music
Thank you for watching!
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Like a New Year's resolution? - Yes!
- Oh, that's good. I'll go tell them one by one.
That's it? - Yeah.
I'll go first.
You want to say it before this?
Well, I guess, in 2024, if I'm the cause of the problem...
Well, as before, we will overcome many obstacles together.
And more and more, I would like to make it a year where I can see wonderful scenery with various observers.
I hope to make it a year in which I can see wonderful scenery with various observers.
Thank you very much.
I will eat a lot of ramen noodles.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm 18 years old, so I'm going to be an adult.
I will be an adult
I'll get more and more physical
That's great!
2024, isn't it 24?
I'll be thinking about myself 24 hours a day.
Even when I'm sleeping.
I don't mean I make you think. I think.
Even when I'm thinking.
I think, as this channel.
I'm here to make you laugh.
Oh!
Can I?
The first laugh of the new year.
Thank you very much.
Can I come in?
It's the New Year, after all.
Now you can have a good laugh.
Thank you for your time.
I'm going overseas.
All right!
It's messy!
I'm going abroad.
I'm going abroad. I'll act when I feel like it.
Where do you want to go most right now?
I'd like to go to America.
If the timing is right, I'd like to travel to various places.
You're all ambitious.
You think I'm ambitious?
I want to eat ramen!
Are you ambitious?
This year is our 5th anniversary!
It goes by so fast!
It's our 5th anniversary, but it's our 5th anniversary since we formed the group, not since we met.
That's amazing.
How many years has it been since we were formed? Since we met.
Six or seven years.
That's fast.
It's about six months after 2024.
It's also our fifth anniversary.
I want you all to know that the game is on you.
I hope to show you the new strength of playing the game by yourself.
I hope to show you the new strength of playing games by yourself.
We will continue to play the game by ourselves in 2024.
Thank you for your support!
Let's make it a great year!
Trick unveiled Kusa Taste Mini minha vida
Today is the first YouTube video of the new year!
Sorry, it's very fluffy!
Let's enjoy the New Year!
I know, I know, I know!
Good plan!
Here it is...
I have a lot of tools to play with.
It's called New Year's play.
I'm going to play with these.
I see.
That's all?
That's all.
Then, can the members do the playing by themselves?
Yes, that's right.
Where would you like to start?
I don't know.
Wouldn't Ryotan be better?
Okay, Ryotan is good.
What do you like?
Oh, this?
Yes, this one.
Koma.
Beyblade.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Name of the product.
All the pieces are Beyblades.
I want to turn the pieces
I grew up on Beyblades.
Piece spinning?
No, you can turn the pieces now, you can turn the pieces now, you can turn the pieces now.
I'll just keep doing it.
Have you ever done that before, by the way?
I've done it before, but I don't know how.
Let's do it.
Let's do it, let's do it.
What was that? That one?
Oh!
He's dead.
I'll spin the pieces.
Piece by piece.
Oh!
Come on, one.
Come on, one time.
Piece by piece
Piece by piece.
Oh, no.
No more spinning?
That's the way to spin it.
Do you know how to spin it?
Spin it around.
Yes, I do.
I'll do it my own way.
Just spin it your own way.
Just spin it.
I'll spin it, I'll spin it, I'll spin it
Oh, my God.
Here it comes.
Can you do it?
Let's go, let's go.
How many times do I have to do it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're full of shit?
Hey, hey, hey.
Like konnyaku string
Turn right.
That's not it.
Turn it the furthest.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Ready?
Yeah, but it's pretty stupid
It's not the way to turn 50,000 It's not the way to turn 50,000
I'm sorry. You're disqualified along with Ms. Ryota
Who's who?
No, it's okay. It's okay. To each his own.
No, no, no, give it your all, give it your all, give it your all
I don't know, maybe I don't understand
It's okay, it's okay
Here we go.
You've done your research.
I see.
Why don't you try Kougo?
Kogo?
It'll leave a vertical line.
I'll do it in kougo.
Oh, God, I can't take this long.
You're right.
Wait a minute.
You just tried to kill me.
That's good, isn't it?
Let's not go for it.
Let's just go for it.
I see it.
I think I see it.
Give me that.
It's much harder to turn with the desk.
It's hard to use a desk.
Is there someone who can spin it here?
Yeah, there is.
You have to do it on the low side.
I haven't done it since elementary school.
I haven't spun a top like this since elementary school.
Me, too. Me too, about that long.
I wonder if it's something you do in class.
A magazine that looks like something I could do.
Oh, that's good.
It looks like something I could do.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I got my English right, too.
You did a great job with the English.
You did a great job with the English, too.
But, you know, there's no groove in this panel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Grooves?
The thread is too stiff.
Do normal frames have grooves?
They fit into the groove, one round at a time.
You're making a good shape.
This, this is good.
This is gonna work.
It's official.
Genji Ma.
It's gonna work, right?
It's going to work.
He'll fall for it.
What do you think?
What's your fortune today? It's on my desk.
What's your fortune for the year, huh?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What?
I'm sure that's right.
What's the right answer?
I really want to do it.
That's probably it.
I'll do the rest with my feet.
What did I do?
I was just setting him up.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, my God.
It's not me, not yet.
Can I go now?
I'm on the desk for now.
I'm number one right now.
Yeah, you're number one.
You got it right.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I can't go that far.
Maybe... maybe this is it.
This is the hard part.
I think I've been...
I think I was putting a lot of effort into it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a matter of how you pull it, isn't it?
From here.
I don't know.
The top comes off.
No, this is hard.
Try this one.
I thought it was supposed to be like this.
Try to take it off.
I don't think it's supposed to be like this.
That looks good.
Oh, yeah.
Hold it down.
Oh, that way.
Oh, my God, it's spinning.
It's spinning in a different way.
It's spinning like crazy.
Oh, my God, it's spinning.
And it's backwards.
Number one so far.
First place so far.
But the guy who spins the top of the top of the top of the top of the top of the top...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to see this.
Oh, man...
Let me show you how to do it.
Can I do a little simulation?
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Let's do a little simulation.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
The simulation worked, didn't it?
What power makes it rotate? You've got to understand that.
This is how it's done, guys.
It's time to go.
It's okay, it's okay.
I really want to do it. I really want to do it.
I really want to do it. Be cooperative.
Be cooperative.
I want to do it!
You can go ahead and do it when it's your time.
Just go. Just go.
At this stage?
It's okay. It's okay.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Uh, uh, uh, uh...
That's what you say to yourself.
You're down, now.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Drop it, drop it
You're right, seriously.
Ryota, on the contrary, you couldn't do it with your hands like this
Seriously, it's so lame
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
If you don't decide at the end, there's still a fallout
No, that's right, let him decide.
Let him decide and it's over.
If Ryota didn't decide, maybe Koma would've won everything he just took
I might have won everything I took.
Yes, for sure.
It's going to work, even like this.
We can do it.
Please, I can do it. I can do it.
Come on, Ryota, show us.
I'm going to fly in 2024.
In 2024.
That's too bad.
If it wasn't for the desk, I could have made it.
I'm sure.
Well, I'll take the King of the Panels championship, then.
I'll take that as a yes.
I'm the only one who can do it.
Wait, wait, wait. You're gonna have to help us all out.
You're right.
Maybe you should try to make them stronger.
All the way stronger.
So, let's start with the 20.
We'll wind it up.
Stronger, so Jun-kun should wind it.
Oh, okay.
Let's do it again.
Go, go, go, go!
Ryota, go, go, go!
Ahhh...
Same as before.
I want to turn it and show you how strong I am.
Can I do it now?
Let's just take this picture.
I'll use the cutter.
I'll use the cutter. I just want to get a shot of you throwing.
That's right, that's right.
Just until the throw. Just until the throw, please.
Okay, then.
Go!
говор Fee
honestly
adjustment - so beautiful, so beautiful, so beautiful a
z No, ei
100th time for time change
Glad to hear it.
Okay, then.
That's all.
This was the day of the production shipment
Thank you very much.
You're done.
New Year's project
Now...
What's his name? Ryota
What's his name?
Hagoita.
I'm going to do Hagoita...
I'm going to do the hagoita.
Hagoita's...
I was called the Champion of the Hagoita.
Where did you get that?
In my hometown?
In a dream.
Excuse me, sir.
Can I have a little heart attack?
Uh, uh, excuse me.
Don't hold up the signal.
What do you mean?
It's a really bad signal.
You, I'll let you make the call.
I bit it.
I'll take those odds.
That's my boy Nagyon.
Ready?
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
You're in.
All right.
I'm with you.
I was quite the pencil pusher.
It's strong.
Oh?